<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Frugivore Dispersal and Landscape Genetics</title>
      <link>/project/frugivore_behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/frugivore_behavior/</guid>
      <description>The influence frugivores can have on the adaption of fruit sources goes beyond selection due to feeding preferences. The behavior of dispersers can affect the direction and strength of gene flow across a landscape. I am interested in how the colonial nesting behavior of a pigeon influence the distribution of genetic diversity of preferred food trees. The White-Crowned Pigeon (Patagioenas leucocephala) is a large bodied Columbid native to the Caribbean and capable of traveling long distances over water during seasonal migration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phenology</title>
      <link>/project/phenology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/phenology/</guid>
      <description>Arabidopsis has long served as a model for basic plant biology questions. We want to use our deep understanding of Arabidopsis biology and genetics to better understand how plants function in their environment and in response to natural conditions. We compare the great natural variation in phenological traits (dormancy, flowering time) across Arabidopsis&amp;rsquo; range to dates of collection of herbarium samples to make sense of the factors controlling life history variation in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phenotypic Change in Herbaria Records</title>
      <link>/project/herbarium_phenotypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/herbarium_phenotypes/</guid>
      <description>Arabidopsis has long served as a model for basic plant biology questions. We want to use our deep understanding of Arabidopsis biology and genetics to better understand how plants function in their environment and in response to natural conditions. We modeled changes in phenotypes (flowering date, C:N, delta15N, delta13C) over time and in response to climate variation to study how Arabidopsis populations have reacted to environmental pressures over the last 200 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Project</title>
      <link>/project/external-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/external-project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>